<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="menu_list_item">
        <item >Explore</item>
        <item >Gallery</item>
        <item >20under20</item>
        <item >Favourite</item>
        <item >Setting</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="photographers_names">
        <item >Evan J Atwood</item>
        <item >Rachel Baran</item>
        <item >Olivia Bee</item>
        <item >Alex Benetel</item>
        <item >Oliver Charles</item>
        <item >Alex Currie</item>
        <item >Silvia Grav</item>
        <item >Zev Hoover</item>
        <item >Katharina Jung</item>
        <item >Lissy Laricchia</item>
        <item >Brian Oldham</item>
        <item >Laurence Philomene</item>
        <item >Greg Ponthus</item>
        <item >Berta Vicente Salas</item>
        <item >Nicholas Scarpinato</item>
        <item >Alex Stoddard</item>
        <item >David Uzochukwu</item>
        <item >Chrissie White</item>
        <item >wiissa</item>
        <item >Lauren Withrow</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photographers_ids">
        <item >75034991@N05</item>
        <item >47776579@N08</item>
        <item >10853447@N06</item>
        <item >27838818@N04</item>
        <item >65516775@N02</item>
        <item >65942669@N05</item>
        <item >63102190@N07</item>
        <item >66603426@N05</item>
        <item >92795766@N04</item>
        <item >37007775@N03</item>
        <item >55407658@N05</item>
        <item >21907940@N03</item>
        <item >57115590@N03</item>
        <item >29473452@N02</item>
        <item >72187820@N08</item>
        <item >48760515@N04</item>
        <item >60882352@N05</item>
        <item >48128761@N00</item>
        <item >38546378@N02</item>
        <item >32928900@N05</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="photographers_cover_image_urls">
        <item >https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7218/7092839051_e5bfc75e8f_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8535/8916700014_00119fe648_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3852/15001573652_729e3c4839_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8068/8227681399_76e6a57797_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm3.staticflickr.com/2914/14550569782_84bb329788_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm6.staticflickr.com/5561/14855714005_c0e423abeb_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm3.staticflickr.com/2815/9672720200_e3157065d4_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm3.staticflickr.com/2864/9160856120_a8e17ceae6_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3847/14692656800_f4a71eaef3_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm7.staticflickr.com/6098/6304393890_a01fd6ecc4_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm3.staticflickr.com/2109/5700338135_b0f85bc911_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3849/14775805747_9815e036c0_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7188/6928728720_97c1ced08f_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm3.staticflickr.com/2442/3823625739_eeca697501_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8494/8323305481_4296220369_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4088/5037955976_1537b30234_b.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3861/15114347211_404f07922f_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm3.staticflickr.com/2752/5825099471_600bfa8c51_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7315/9701860090_ce626204b9_c.jpg</item>
        <item >https://farm4.staticflickr.com/3896/14592913446_2629c03939_c.jpg</item>
    </string-array>


    <array name="photographer_author_evaluate">
        <item >Evan James Atwood currently lives in Flagstaff, Arizona, and took an interest in photography
            exploring self-portraiture through a 365 project in 2012. This experience nurtured a passion for
            the visual arts and a fascination with expressing the darker range of human emotions. His work,
            however, often contains a strong element of hope and depicts simple moments with a cinematic quality.</item>
        <item >Rachel Baran is a fine art photographer whose work centers around conceptual self\-portraits.
            Even though Baran has received no formal training in photography or graphic design, her work has
            been recognized internationally on blogs such as My Modern Metropolis and on multiple book covers,
            and even taken her overseas under commission, displaying her photographic techniques at the \"Festival
            Week\-end au bord de l\'eau\" music festival in Sierre, Switzerland, this past summer.</item>
        <item >Olivia Bee is a 20\-year\-old photographer and director from Portland, Oregon, who is based in
            Brooklyn, New York. She is intrigued by the beauty of everyday life and how the beauty of memories
            (real or imagined) touches us. Her portfolio includes portraits (The New York Times Magazine, TeenNick),
            lifestyle (Converse, Adidas, Nike), and fashion (Hermès, Harper\'s Bazaar, Numero, Vogue.com, Roger
            Vivier).</item>
        <item >Alex is from Sydney, Australia, and became interested in photography after taking a visual design
            course. She has since been published in Russia\'s Harper\'s Bazaar, showcased her work in Sydney, and
            has been fortunate enough to travel, meet and collaborate with other artists. Alex\’s work captures
            mysterious yet dreamlike worlds, filled with oddities that encompass aspects of reality.</item>
        <item >Oliver Charles\’ interest in photography began at a young age, and he has since built a collection
            of work which expresses the surreal and often dark stages of human emotion. Oliver juxtaposes dreaming
            and reality by capturing people in dreamlike scenarios but located in natural environments. Oliver is
            currently based in London, where he is studying digital photography at Ravensbourne College.</item>
        <item >Alex Currie is a photographer and filmmaker from Buffalo, New York. His photographs focus on
            conveying a story in a single frame and evoking a strong emotional connection with the viewer.</item>
        <item >Silvia Grav was born in Basque Country. She started in fine arts, but was frustrated and left
            during her second year to devote herself to improving her photography on her own. Since then, she has
            appeared in several major magazines and blogs, continuously working on artwork for various musicians
            and has been involved in various new projects.</item>
        <item >Zev Hoover is a 15\-year\-old lad with a camera. He tries to capture the beauty in loneliness, the
            beauty of being a very small person in a very big place. In addition to exhibits, there have been blogs,
            books, newspaper and magazines articles, and a BBC documentary on his work. When not taking pictures,
            he likes designing, building, flying and oftentimes crashing large foam\-board remote\-controlled airplanes
            equipped with cameras.</item>
        <item >Katharina is a fine\-art and portrait photographer from Hermeskeil, Germany. Since February 2013,
            she converts her daydreams into images. After finishing her diploma as a media designer in June 2014
            she will go to Bali and travel thorugh New Zealand with her camera.</item>
        <item >Lissy (Elle) Laricchia is a 20\-year\-old photographer from Ontario, Canada (but currently resides
            in New York City), with a large online presence of over 80,000 followers. Her work predominantly centers
            around feelings of nostalgia and feeding her inner child. Her photos have appeared in fashion, photography,
            and literary magazines, on book and album covers, in stores, and have inspired a music video. They have also
            been exhibited internationally.</item>
        <item >Brian Oldham is a freelance fine\-art photographer, specializing in the surreal and conceptual realms.
            Brian grew up, and still lives and works, near Los Angeles.</item>
        <item >Laurence Philomene is a Montreal\-based freelance photographer. She started taking pictures and posting
            them online when she was 14 and hasn’t stopped since, developing her own dreamy, pastel\-hued aesthetic.
            Nowadays, you can find her at home playing with dolls, taking care of her birds, napping and taking pictures
            that explore themes of gender identity, femininity, girlhood, and color.</item>
        <item >Greg Ponthus is a photographer who grew in the countryside of Lyon, where he lived in golden light and
            grassy hills. He moved from France two years ago to attend an art school in Brussels. He stole his first
            camera from his dad when he was 15 or so and immediately started shooting people he lived with.</item>
        <item >Berta Vicente is a Spanish photographer who started taking pictures of her friends at the age of 14.
            She continues to learn and explore, and currently exhibits her work in art galleries in Barcelona,
            London and Paris.</item>
        <item >Nicholas Scarpinato is a photographer based out of Richmond, VA. From an early age he was trained in
            classical painting, sculpture, and drawing but later found photography and filmmaking to be his passion.
            He currently studies photography and filmmaking at Virginia Commonwealth University.</item>
        <item >Alex Stoddard was born in Jacksonville, Florida, and spent his childhood in the deep south. He began
            taking self\-portraits at the age of 16 in the woods behind his home in Georgia, and this stirred in him
            the need to create and express himself through the craft of photography. Through his work, Alex creates
            dark and fantastical tales that capture the drama and fragility of the human experience.</item>
        <item >David Uzochukwu was born in December 1998 in Innsbruck, Austria. He delved into photography at the
            age of 10, and focused on self-portraiture and fine art photography after having fallen in love with
            the craft.</item>
        <item >Chrissie White is a photographer from Seattle who is always searching for magic in the nature that
            surrounds us all. Her childhood was spent exploring snow\-covered mountains and sailing through the glittering
            sea, which has greatly influenced her passion for adventure. When she isn\'t seeing new places, she likes to
            dream of faraway worlds where anything is possible.</item>
        <item >Vanessa and Wilson are a photography duo from Miami, Florida. They met when they were 14- and
            15\-years\-old, and have been together since. They shoot exclusively film, and love lots of color, sunshine
            and the seventies.</item>
        <item >Lauren Withrow was born in Texas and began photographing at the age of 15. Growing up in a small southern
            town, Withrow finds inspiration in the vast landscapes and dirt roads within the Texas countryside. Withrow\'s
            focus is on cinematic portraiture and is currently in development of her first film.</item>
    </array>


</resources>
